easybodyfit.com 2016-05-03

# Privacy Policy - Easy Body Fitness

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. We strictly enforce our privacy policy. We want to make your venture as enjoyable and rewarding as possible.

This Privacy Policy is to demonstrate our seriousness in your well-being and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our Company collects information, who accesses stored information, and how it is stored. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Easy Body Fit collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http://www.easybodyfit.com](http://www.easybodyfit.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Easy Body Fit.

 **Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, [features](http://www.easybodyfit.com/features/ "features") or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

 **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

 **Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

 **How we use collected information**

Easy Body Fit may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To improve customer service

Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

– To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

– To improve our Site

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

 **How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

 **Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

 **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non-personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

Easy Body Fit has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Personal Information Our Company Collects and How It Is Used

Our company collects information in different ways from new affiliates and members who opt-in to our program. We use this information solely to provide affiliates and members with our products and services. We do not, under any circumstance, disclose personal information collected.

 **Registration:** Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Products or Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), SSN. The personal information collected from members during the registration process is used to deliver products. This information is not shared with third parties. Social Security Numbers are collected for tax purposes. This information is held with extreme confidentiality on a computer disconnected from any kind of internet service.

 **Online Shopping:** At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide [contact](http://www.easybodyfit.com/pages/contact/ "contact") information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information.

If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient’s name, address, and phone number. Our company has no control over the third parties’ use of any personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so.

If you order services or products directly from our company we will use the personal information you provide only to process that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

 **Responses to Email Inquiries:** When visitors or members send email inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Our company does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

 **Voluntary Customer Surveys:** We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of products and services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary.

 **Public Forums:** Please remember that any information you may disclose in any Member Directory, or other public areas of our Web sites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

 **Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practiced described herein, you may [contact us](http://www.easybodyfit.com/contact-us/ "contact us") through the [contact](http://www.easybodyfit.com/contact/ "contact") information provided on this web site.

 **Revisions to This Policy:** Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms of Service agreement, and our other policies and agreements at any time in any manner, by updating this posting.
